export const QUESTIONS = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What will be the output of: print(type([]))",
    options: ["<class 'dict'>", "<class 'list'>", "<class 'set'>", "<class 'tuple'>"],
    answerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "In BGMI, if your gun has no ammo, that's like",
    options: ["Empty array", "Null pointer exception", "Stack overflow", "Deadlock"],
    answerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Which symbol is used for comments in Python?",
    options: ["//", "/* */", "#", "---"],
    answerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What will be the output of this code?: x=5; x+=3; print(x)",
    options: ["5", "8", "53", "Error"],
    answerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Which of these is NOT an OOPs concept?",
    options: ["Inheritance", "Polymorphism", "Encapsulation", "Compilation"],
    answerIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What does len('Hello') return in Python?",
    options: ["4", "5", "6", "Error"],
    answerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "If BGMI adds a new map update, it's like",
    options: ["Installing a new module", "Debugging code", "Creating a new object", "Running a loop"],
    answerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "In the context of the OSI Model, what is the total number of layers?",
    options: ["5", "7", "9", "11"],
    answerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which of the following components has the greatest impact on BGMI frame rate (FPS) performance on a smartphone?",
    options: ["RAM size", "Processor (CPU & GPU)", "Storage type", "Battery capacity"],
    answerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What will be the output of this C code?: int i; for(i=0; i < 5; i++); { printf('%d', i); }",
    options: ["0 1 2 3 4", "5", "4", "Error"],
    answerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "Which of these data structures works on the principle of LIFO (Last In, First Out)?",
    options: ["Queue", "Array", "Stack", "Linked List"],
    answerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "In C programming, what is the correct format specifier for printing an integer?",
    options: ["%f", "%d", "%c", "%s"],
    answerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "What will be the output of this Python code: def add(x, y=5): return x+y; print(add(10))",
    options: ["10", "15", "Error", "None"],
    answerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "What does the '==' operator do in most programming languages?",
    options: ["Assigns a value", "Compares two values for equality", "Checks memory address", "Declares a variable"],
    answerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "What is the main function of DNS on the internet?",
    options: ["Store website content", "Translate domain names into IP addresses", "Increase browsing speed", "Manage cookies"],
    answerIndex: 1,
  },
];
